

CONTACT

PHONE:

082167161247

EMAIL:

swetahutauruk@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sweta-

hutauruk-5b621817a/

GITLAB:

https://gitlab.com/SwetaHutauruk

ORGANIZATIONS

- Secretary of Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa (BEM) Institut Teknologi Del (06/2019 – 06/2020)
- Secretary of Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika Institut Teknologi Del (HIMATIF) (09/2018 – 09/2019)
- Commitee PCA Institut Teknologi Del (06/2018 – 10/2018)

AWARD RECEIVED

- Secretary of Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa (BEM) Institut Teknologi Del (06/2019 – 06/2020)
- The 2019 ICPC Indonesia IDEAFUSE UI/UX Competition
- Scholarship of DICODING as Students MADE (Menjadi Android Developer Expert (2019)
- Scholarship of Yayasan St. Nahanson Parapat (08/2014 – 06/2017)

SWETA MARITO HUTAURUK

PROFILE

Information Technology student at Del Institute of Technology. I have experience about make documenter system, design (UI), building and testing Web and Android Application I'm confident that I'll be a strong join with your team and I have lot experience work team. I have a good interpersonal communication and can work under pressure.

EDUCATION

INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI DEL

D3 Teknologi Informasi | September 2017 – September 2020

SMK St. Nahanson Parapat Sipoholon

Teknik Komputer & Jaringan | June 2014 – June 2017

PROJECTS

- Rancang Bangun Sistem Informasi Kemahasiswaan Institut
 Teknologi Del dengan Metode Scrum Team work, Yii2 framework, used Gitlab as repository, Scrum, Trello, use Gant chart
- Manajemen KP (Kerja Praktek) IT Del Team work, Yii2 framework, Gitlab, SDLC, documenter of system requirement.
- Aplikasi Android Post Team work, Android Studio, Java
- Online Vehicle Toba Team work, Php, Html5, javascript

EXPERIENCE

- Web Developer Internship at Dinas Penanaman Modal dan Pelayanan Perizinan Terpadu Satu Pintu (June 2020 – July 2020) Adobe Xd, Yii2 Framework, documenter of system requirement, github.
- Web Developer Internship at PT Sikkola Medan (June 2019 August 2019)
 - Team work, laravel, designed UI by Corel Draw, Adobe XD.
- Full Stack Developer & Scrum Master (Oktober 2019 June 2020) Rancang Bangun Sistem Informasi Kemahasiswaan Institut Teknologi Del dengan Metode Scrum (web development)
- UI/UX Design Competition (21 June 2019 22 June 2019) at Mikroskil Medan

SKILLS & TECHNOLOGY

Programming Languages & Frameworks Editors -Yii2 Framework -Android Studio -Star UML -PHP -Laravel -Sublime text -Bizagi -C++ -RESTful API -Netbeans -Oracle -Java -Javascript -Vs Code -MySQL